meritline.com 2002-02-05

# Meritline.com :DVD-R Blank Media, CD-R MEDIA , Compactflash CARD,SMARTMEDIA CARD , HP, Epson Ink Jet Cartridges Privacy Policy

| | 

_This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience. Please see the[Yahoo! Privacy Policy](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/) for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information._

* * *

**We are committed to protecting your privacy online.**   
We created our Privacy Policy("Policy") in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to protecting the privacy of our shoppers. 

Questions regarding this Policy should be directed to.  
Sales@Meritline.com

* * *

**  
Security Issue**

Question : What kind of security do you use?  
Answer : We use the Stronghold secure server, currently the second best selling secure server software, and in our opinion, technically the best product. It supports industry-standard 128-bit SSL encryption.

**About Security...**  
All online transactions at Yahoo! Stores are handled with industry-standard SSL encryption.

When you enter your credit card number into the order form, it is transmitted across the Internet in an encrypted (scrambled) form, then decoded when it gets to us.

For added security, we also encrypt the credit card number when it is stored on disk, and when we forward it to the merchant.

If you are not the kind of person who worries about being hit by lightning as you're crossing the street, you probably don't have to worry that your credit card number will be intercepted on the way to a secure Web site. According to CNN, 

> **"The prevalent opinion...is that on-line credit card use is actually no riskier for consumers than traditional "low-tech" transactions."**

We order products online all the time, both as a company and as individuals. When we use a credit card to buy something online, we feel at least as safe as we would using one in a store or restaurant.

* * *

**What information does Meritline.com collect from you?**  
In order to better provide you with numerous products and services, We collect two types of information about its visitors: Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information. Our primary goal in collecting information from you is to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and customized experience while using our site.  

* * *

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information**  
This refers to information that does not by itself identify a specific individual. We gather certain information about you based upon where you shop on our site in several ways. This information is compiled and analyzed on both a personal and an aggregated basis. This information may include the Web site's Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") that you just came from, which URL you next go to, what browser you are using, and your Internet Protocol ("IP") address. A URL is the global address of documents and other resources on the World Wide Web. An IP address is an identifier for a computer or device on a Transmission Control Protocol/Internet Protocol ("TCP/IP") network, such as the World Wide Web. Networks like the web use the TCP/IP protocol to route information based on the IP address of the destination. In other words, an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the web, allowing web servers to locate and identify your computer. Computers require IP addresses in order for users to communicate on the Internet, browse and shop.

* * *

**Shopping**  
We collect IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, to gather broad demographic information, to enable ads to be served on our site, to report Non-Personally Identifiable Information to our advertisers, and to monitor the level of activity on our site. We collect information from visitors to our site regarding the URLs they came from, their IP addresses, domain types (e.g., .com or .org), the browser type used to come to the site, the country, state and telephone area code where their servers are located, the pages of our site that visitors viewed during their visit, and any search terms entered on our site.   

* * *

**Ordering**  
When you order from us, we collect personally identifiable information from you. If you order one of our products or services, we will collect and maintain your name, e-mail address, billing address, shipping address, telephone number, product selections, credit card or other payment information, order number, referring URL, IP address and a password. We collect this, and other information, as disclosed in this Policy, in order to fill your order, to communicate with you about your order and to send you promotional materials via email. Before confirming your order, you will have the opportunity to review the product order form and make changes and additions to the information it contains and these changes will be automatically kept for future use. **We do not accept Walk-in or will call orders. All walk-in or will call will only be accepted with advance arrangement.**  

* * *

**Online Surveys and Polling**  
In order to improve our services to you, we ask some of our customers to voluntarily complete surveys, which may be collected by an independent third party. Individual survey answers are confidential, although Non-Personally Identifiable Information is collected and disclosed to third parties. If you do not wish to participate in a survey, simply decline to participate when asked.   

* * *

**Contact Information and Third Party Data**  
If you contact Meritline or our customer service representatives by telephone, e-mail or letter, we may keep a record of your correspondence or comments. If you report a problem with our site, we may collect such information in a file specific to you. If you contact us through our feedback area or by calling one of our customer service representatives, we may ask for your name and e-mail address in order to send you a reply. If other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or purchases on our site, we may keep the information in a file specific to you.   

* * *

**Surveys and Polling**  
We use a third party surveyor to run optional surveys for Meritline.com. That surveyor collects Non-Personally Identifiable Information for the sole purpose of providing reports to Meritline.com about our shoppers' interests and opinions.  

* * *

**Fulfillment**  
The information collected by Meritline.com is used only for the limited purposes of processing orders, keeping you informed about your order status, for statistical purposes, for improving our site and its performance, to serve ads, and to notify you of products or special offers that may be of interest to you. We will disclose your Personally Identifiable Information to third parties to charge your credit card, fill your order, deliver your order, and provide customer service.. For example, we must release your credit card information to the card-issuing bank to confirm payment; and release your address and telephone information to the delivery service to deliver products that you ordered.  

* * *

**Other Parties**  
We may release account information when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions or to protect the rights, property, and safety of Meritline.com, our users, or others. If customers do not pay us for products ordered, we may submit their account information to a third party collection agency.   

* * *

**Services Provided on Our Site**  
Except as otherwise stated in this Policy, at present Meritline.com does not disclose its customers' Personally Identifiable Information to other merchants.   

* * *

**Compliance with Service of Process or Law Enforcement**  
Occasionally Meritline.com may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide Personally Identifiable Information to the appropriate governmental authorities. We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information upon receipt of a court order, subpoena, or to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation. Meritline.com fully cooperates with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful.   

* * *

**What security precautions are in place to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information?**  
At Meritline.com you can be assured that your personal and account information is secure, consistent with current industry standards. The importance of security for all Personally Identifiable Information associated with our customers is of utmost concern to us. Our secure servers protect the information using advanced firewall technology.  

* * *

**When you access your account information, the information is kept on a secure server.**  
All of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access by physical security means.   

* * *

**Contacting Meritline.com about privacy questions or concerns**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact Meritline.com by sending a letter to: 

Attn: Customer Service  
Meritline.com  
14909 Clark Ave. Suite B  
City of Industry

You may also contact us by e-mail at sales@Meritline .com
